Why I reviewed my car insurance
policy and why you should too.
Hi I'm Wil Alexander an injury attorney.
I want to tell you a story about myself.
When I first started
practicing injury law,
I didn't realize a lot about
my own personal car insurance.
So what I quickly realized was there's
these different coverages out there that
people really don't know about.
So most people think, oh,
I'll get car insurance when
I get my license, I have
to have it, it's state law,
got to have car insurance - so in case
I hit someone else that they can recover
from that for the property damage
or for potentially an injury claim.
But what I didn't realize was that I
had the opportunity to purchase what's
called Underinsured Motorist Coverage.
So there's different coverages out there
that you can talk with your insurance
agent about,
about getting car insurance that can
protect you from if someone else hits you.
So there's MedPay coverage,
there is underinsured motorist coverage,
there's uninsured motorist
coverage, which you have to have,
but this underinsured coverage
I really didn't know about.
And what that does is,
let's say that I'm driving down the road
and someone hits me that has minimum
state limits. So in South
Carolina, that's a 25/50 policy.
So that means that I can only recover
$25,000 from the at-fault person.
But if I have this
Underinsured Motorist Coverage,
I could collect off of my own insurance
to take back what was taken from me and
to pay my medical bills pay for lost
wages and other damages that I had because
someone hit me in a wreck.
So it's something that you
really should think about.
Most people, again,
I think they only think about well I
get car insurance to protect if I hit
someone else.
But there are these different coverages
out there that can protect you,
your own insurance that can protect you
and your family if someone hits you when
you're driving down the road and
they don't have adequate insurance.
So I'd really encourage you to reach
out to me if you'd like for me to review
your policy. I'd love to do that.
Let you know what coverages you have.
Your insurance agent definitely talk
with them and understand what these
different coverages are
because importantly,
if you don't have that coverage
and you get in a wreck,
you can't then go get it. It's
either you have it or you don't.
So it's something that you need to
think about to protect yourself,
to protect your family,
and something that a lot of people I
think really overlook that they don't
understand.
And even I really did not understand it
until I got into the personal injury law
practice. So really encourage you to look
into that. If you have any questions,
feel free to shoot me an
email, text our number,
any way you can reach out to me.
I'd be glad to answer any
questions that you have.